Oh, there it was.
ああ、いた
I want it.
俺が欲しいわよ
I can have that child.
俺はあの子を貰えるんだよ
You're full.
お腹いっぱいだね
Let's be quiet a little longer.
もうちょい黙ろうね
what?
なに?
Mountain?
山?
Isn't your mother a nuisance at a time like this?
こんな時間にお母さんが迷惑でしょ?
It's such a nuisance.
迷惑ってあんないじゃん
something.
何か
Well then, let's make a little sound so that my mother notices.
じゃあ母さんに気付くように、ちょっと響かせよう
rhythm?
リズム?
I want to go home.
帰りたい
feeling
気持
Is it okay?
ち いい?
Do you feel better?
気持ちよくなった?
I'm really going back.
本当に帰ります
No, when I go home.
いや、帰ると
It came.
来てした
I'm going home.
帰ります
帰る
Because I've already heard that.
もうそれ聞いたから
wait a minute.
ちょっと 待って
Because I've already heard that.
もうそれ聞いたから
Right away.
すぐ
Really soon.
本当にすぐ
About 10 seconds left.
もうあと10秒くらい
I'm going home.
帰ります
I can actually give you money and make phone calls.
本当お金も渡すし、電話もできるから
I'll contact you as soon as it's finished.
終わってから早く連絡
It's 10 seconds.
10秒でしょ
It's almost here.
もうつく
very soon.
もうすぐ
Wait quick.
早く待って
Let's call.
電話しよう
I'll just bring my phone.
電話ちょっと持ってくるから
I'll bring the phone.
電話持ってくるんだよ
Let's call.
電話しよう
I'll bring it.
持ってくる
I brought my phone.
電話持ってきた
That's fine, right?
いいでしょ
In the meantime.
その間に
Until I get a phone call.
電話あるまでね
Raise your feet.
足上げて
電話
You can't come in, right?
入らないでしょ
Good at it.
上手い
電
We talked.
話 した
Where did it go?
どこいった?
Where did you go?
どこいったの?
I'll bring the phone.
電話持ってくるから
I don't have a phone.
電話ないよ
It's okay, it'll be over soon.
すぐ終わりするから大丈夫
It'll end.
終わるからね
sorry.
ごめん
Sorry.
ごめんね
Because it's work.
仕事だから
hey.
ね
I'm also getting paid.
お金ももらってるし
Because I'm getting paid.
お金もらってるから
You got it, right?
もらってたよね
money.
お金
You got it, right?
もらってたでしょ
You got it too, didn't you?
も らってたでしょ
You got it, right?
もらってたでしょ
money.
お金
It's okay to cry.
泣いてもいいね
Here you go.
ほら、ここね
Is it because you received it?
受け取っているからしょ?
Because you received it, right?
受 け取っているからしょ?
Look.
ほ ら
Shall we come back?
帰ってきましょ?
I'm going home.
帰りに行きます
You want it, right?
欲しいでしょ?
I don't need money.
お金いらない
yeah?
ん?
Because I am receiving it.
受け取っているから
It's okay if you don't need it.
いらないことは大丈夫
Yeah.
うん
It's okay.
無 事に大丈夫
Yeah.
うん
I want to go home.
帰りに行きたい
Can I take it out?
出していい?
Yeah.
うん
I'll take it out.
出していくよ
It's really coming out.
めちゃくちゃ出てんじゃん
It's not going inside anymore.
もう中には出てないね
Yeah.
うん
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Because everything is outside.
全部外に出てるから
Isn't that okay?
そんなんいいでしょ?
Because it doesn't come out inside.
中には出てないから
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It felt so good.
めっちゃ気持ちよかった
Just a little bit,
ちょっとさ、
How is it?
どう だっけ?
wait a minute.
ちょっと 待って
Is it okay?
いいの?
Goth is over too.
ゴスも終わりだからね
You did your best.
頑張ったね
Can I go home?
帰れますか?
Just a little, that's all.
ちょっとさ、 これだけ
Hey, please write this down.
ちょっとじゃあ、 これ書いてもらって
Just a little bit.
ちょっと だけ
Because I can go home.
帰れるから
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Just a phone call.
電話だけ
On the way home.
帰りに帰りに
電話
Okay.
いいよ
Ask me to write it.
書いてもらって
Let me write.
書かせて
Then write it down and give me a call.
じゃあ書いたら、 電話かけて
That's terrible.
やばいな
strawberry.
イチゴ
Eat strawberries.
イチゴ食べる
You can eat strawberries.
イチゴ食べていいよ
That's terrible.
やばいな
Oh my goodness.
や ばいね
I want to do Volme.
ボルメやりたいな
what happened?
どうしたの?
what up?
どう した?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Did something happen?
何かあった?
Sorry.
ごめんね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
What should I do?
ちょっとどうしよう?
stop?
止める?
Ah, I went.
あ、いった
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Sorry.
ごめんね
It's over now.
もうおしまいね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
You did your best.
頑張ったね
hey.
ね
money.
お金
Go home.
帰って
I did my best.
頑張った
a little bit.
ちょっと
Is it over already?
もう終わりかな?
wait a minute.
ちょっと 待って
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
Sorry.
ごめんね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
a little bit.
ちょっと
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
Quickly, quickly.
早く、早く
Did something happen?
何かあったの?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It was dirty, right?
汚れてたでしょ?
It was dirty, so I did it like this.
汚れてたから、こうやって
yes.
はい
Is it over?
終わりかな?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
Look.
ほら
copper?
どう?
It's over, is it over?
終わり、終わりかな?
copper?
どう?
This time it was Sato.
この時はサトウだったね
hey.
ね
Sorry.
ごめんね
I want to go home.
帰りたいよ
帰りたい
I'll go home.
帰るから
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Because I was doing it.
やってたから
Just do a little bit.
ちょっとだけやって
Park.
パクって
If you copy it, it's over.
パクってやったら終わるから
Park.
パクって
in,
で、
Just Park is fine.
パ クだけでいいから
Park.
パク
Get it down.
下出して
Because it will end.
終わるから
Fake it already.
もうパクして
Park.
パク
Can't you?
できない?
So sit down for a second.
じゃあ、ちょっと座って
Sit down.
座って
good?
いい?
I want to go home.
帰りたい
what?
何?
scared.
怖い
Feels good.
気 持 ちいい
Why do you hate it?
なんで嫌がるの?
feeling
気持ち
good?
いい?
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
Do you feel good?
気 持 ちいい?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Hey.
ね え
dangerous.
危ない
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Sorry.
ごめんね
I hit my head.
頭あぶつけちゃったね
Hey, I wanted to come.
ねえ、来たかったね
You have to deal with me properly.
ちゃんと俺付き合わせないと
Feels good.
気持ちいい
cute.
か わいい
かわいい
It'll be over soon.
すぐ終わるから
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
Look here.
こっち見て
Okay.
いいよ
You can go home.
帰っていいからね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Can I take it out like this?
このまま出していい?
Just now.
さっきね
I felt sorry for her.
かわいそうだったから
Outside.
外にね
But that's okay.
でもいいですよ
Why do you hate it?
なんで嫌がるの?
Why?
どうして?
Because I can have a child?
子 供できちゃうから?
I can't.
できないよ
Even if I say, I can't do it.
俺いってもできないから
good?
いい?
No?
ダメ?
Well then, let's put it on your breasts.
じゃあ、さあ、おっぱいにかけちゃおう
Hey.
ね え
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Look.
ほら
Shall I try writing it carefully?
よくかいてみる?
Shall I try writing?
かいてみる?
Were you interested?
興味あった?
It's okay now, right?
もう大丈夫でしょ?
Please wait for the phone.
電話、待ってくれ
Because I didn't have a phone.
電話なかったからさ
Isn't there one?
いるんでしょ?
That's fine.
それでいいじゃん
nice.
いい ね
A little bit kinky.
ちょっとキンキン